迈克:行了.我在这.我们可以吃饭.
Mike: Alright.I'm here.We can eat.
马克:晚饭还要等会,迈克.开萝尔还在商店.
Maggie: Dinner will be a minute mike.Carol is at the store.
迈克:啊,当一切就绪,就免费?
Mike: Ah, when it's ready, will it be free?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes.
迈克:那样我就等.
Mike: Then I'll stay.
杰森:恩,孩子,这条鱼真,恩,臭.
Jason: Hmmm, boy those fish sticks sure, um, smell.
麦琪:我们在等调味酱.
Maggie: We are waiting for tartar sauce.
本:开萝尔回来了吗?
Ben: Is Carol back yet?
麦琪:别急,本.晚饭等会就好..
Maggie: Relax Ben.Dinner's going to be a while.
本:这不是晚饭.她好像去买卫生纸了.
Ben: Its not dinner.She was supposed to buy toilet paper.
迈克,你有卫生纸吗?
Mike, do you have any toilet paper?
迈克:没有.我从不买那玩意儿.我偷你的.
Mike: No.I never buy the stuff.I steal yours.
天那,你们不会对我想的很多,是吗?
Gosh, you guys don_t think very much of me do you?
麦琪和杰森:不会.
Maggie and jason: No.
开萝尔:如果你傻得会做那事,那你也会傻的去告诉他们.
Carol: If you are dumb enough to do it,
说吧.
then you are dumb enough to tell them about it.Speak!
克莉丝:那……
Chrissy: Well...
克莉丝:哦,你以为你那么可爱,一头卷发,
Carol: Oh, you think you are so cute with that curly hair,
永恒的笑容,好脾气.你让我恶心.
unending smile and happy disposition.You make me puke.
杰森:发生什么事了,开萝尔?
Jason: What's going on Carol?
迈克:是呀,但是更重要的是,调味酱在哪儿?
Mike: Yeah, and more importantly, where is the tartar sauce?
开萝尔:迈克,这比调味酱更重要.
Carol: Mike, this is bigger than tartar sauce.
本:卫生纸在哪儿?
Ben: Where's the toilet paper.
开萝尔:我们没有调味酱.我们没有卫生纸.
Carol: We have no tartar sauce.Wehave no toilet paper.We have no groceries.
我们没有任何东西.那么为什么我们什么都没有,克莉丝?
And why don't we have any groceries Chrissy?
克莉丝:有个脸上很脏很穷的女人,
Chrissy: There was a lady who was needy with a dirty face and I gave her
我就把要买东西的钱给她.
the grocery money.
开萝尔:你怎么能这么自私?
Carol: How selfish can you be?
一个饿鬼在超市里面干什么?
What is a hungry person doing inside a supermarket?
杰森:开萝尔,快点,我们要迟到了.
Jason: Carol, come on, we are going to be late.
麦琪:亲爱的,我不敢肯定这是否仍然是个好主意.
Maggie: Honey, in the light of day I'm not so sure this is such a good idea anymore.
杰森:哦,你开玩笑.在免费诊所,她会遇到一些人,他们不太走运,但他们不是寄生虫,社会渣滓,或者失败者.
Jason: Oh, you're kidding.Down at the free clinic she is going to meet some
people who are down on their luck, who are not freeloaders, misfits and losers
麦琪:那可能发生,是的.
Maggie: Well that could happen, yes.
杰森:我是说,昨天晚上我简直不能相信,
Jason: I mean last night I couldn't believe the way she was talking Maggie.
她会那样说话,麦琪.我是说,
I mean I don't remember ever being so disappointed in one of our children.
我不记得哪个孩子会令我如此失望.她从哪儿学的没有同情心?
Where did she get that insensitivity?
麦琪:那么你在说我是个坏母亲?
Maggie: So you are saying I'm a bad mother?
杰森:不是,麦琪.
Jason: No Maggie.
麦琪:请原谅我有点担心女儿和危险人物来往.
Maggie: Well excuse me for being a little concerned about our daughter hanging out with dangerous people.
杰森:麦琪,我已经和这些人工作六个月了.
Jason: Maggie, I have been working with these people for six months.
麦琪:杰森,你和那些人工作几个月是有原因的.
Maggie: Jason, there is a reason you've been working with them for months.
杰森:也许你应该出来和当义工.
Jason: Maybe you ought to come down and volunteer.
麦琪:我也想过这,我只是在寻找个合适的周末.
Maggie: Well I've thought about it and I've just been looking for the
嘿,我有主意了.我给你开张支票.
right weekend.Hey, I've got an idea.I'll just write you a check.
杰森:麦琪,
Jason: Maggie, we do amazing things down there.
我们在那儿干令人惊异的事情.那是我真正信任的地方.
It's a place I really believe in.
你真认为我会把我的女儿置于危险之中?
You honestly think I'd put my daughter in danger?
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: No.
杰森:而且说到底,她是个足够聪明的女孩.我有这种预感,我想她会明白这是一段宝贵的经历的.
Jason: And underneath, she's a smart enough girl.I have a gut feeling that she
is going to see this as a very worthwhile experience
开萝尔:好了.我准备好了.让这个噩梦结束吧.
Carol: Alright.I'm ready.Let's get this nightmare over with.
杰森:过来,开萝尔.这边走.
Jason: Come on Carol.This way.
沿着这走到右边,那儿就是大夫们的办公室.
Right along here to the right are where all the doctor' s offices are.
在这你会看见那有,啊,你在干吗?
Here you'll see that there is, uh, what are you doing?
开萝尔:拿掉所有的首饰.
Carol: Getting rid of all my jewelry.
杰森:行了.
Jason: Come on.
韦伯斯特:哎.你掉了这个.
Webster: Excuse me.You dropped this.
杰森:谢谢,韦伯斯特.那么你从这点学到了什么?
Jason: Thank you Webster.And what have we learned from this?
开萝尔:他们在看着我.他们都在看着我.
Carol: They are watching me.They are all watching me.
杰森:行了.这是一间主会议室,那些死人过来以他们的方式通过小组会议,
Jason: AlrightThis is the main conference room.
这样他们就能回到大街上去讨,去借,去偷就像你这样的人.
This is where all those dead beats come
to fake their way through group sessions, so they can go back on the street
and beg, borrow and steal from people like you
开萝尔:啊哈.
Carol: Uh hu.
杰森:开萝尔,我在开玩笑.
Jason: Carol, I was being sarcastic.
开萝尔:我知道你开玩笑,爸爸.
Carol: I know you were dad.And I also know why you brought me here.
而且我也知道为什么你带我来这里.那样我可以见到那些比我还糟糕的人.
So that I can see that there are other people worse off than me.
杰森:你什么时候变成公主了?
Jason: When did you become such a Princess?
开萝尔:啊!
Carol: Hu!I am not a Princess.
我可不是公主.现在我们能不能做完这些无意义的事情,
Now can we just get this pointless exercise over with so that I can go
那我还可以回家去睡一会儿?
home and take a nap?
开萝尔:社区健康诊所.啊哈.
Carol: Community health clinic.Uh hu.Uh hu.
啊哈.哦,
Oh I'm sorry; we can not give prescriptions over the phone.
对不起;我们不能在电话里提供处方的.而且顺便说一下,我认为那药是非法的.
And by the way, I don't think that is a legal drug.
听着,你没有必要说粗话.
Well you don't have to be rude about it.
请原谅,但是那是医学上不可能的.
Excuse me but that is anatomically impossible.
男人:请问,饭堂开门了吗?
Man: Excuse me, is the food bank open?
开萝尔:时间是一点到四点.在这签名.姓先写,名后写.
Carol: The hours are one to four.Sign in here.Last name first, first name last.
男人:哦,我不是来这吃饭的;我是来这送饭的.
Man: Oh, I'm not here to get food; I'm here to give food.
开萝尔:哦,哦,对不起.
Carol: Oh, oh I'm sorry.
男人:你看起来很苗条.瞧我,每天锻炼几个小时,就是为了保持苗条和匀称.你看起来眼熟.
Man: For your information thin is in.See I put in long hours at the
spa to keep my body lean and mean.You look familiar
开萝尔:你去哥伦比亚大学?
Carol: Do you go to Columbia?
男人:只是去小便.等等.把你的鼻子抬起来,就好像你闻到臭味一样.
Man: Only the P.Hold on.You stick your nose up in the air like you smell somet5hing bad.
开萝尔:不是.
Carol: No.
男人:是呀,我认识你.你坐一号火车.
Man: Yeah, I know you.You take the number one train.
开萝尔:我不认识你.
Carol: Well I don't know you.
男人:我每天卖给你纽约时报.
Man: I sell you the New York Times every day.
开萝尔:哦,是的.是,当然.很高兴在工作之余见到你.
Carol: Oh, yes.Yes of course.How nice to see you outside of work.
韦伯斯特:这些黑鬼也让我过敏.
Webster: These black people get on my nerves too.
女士:好吧.让我们的少年犯都到这边来.我是你们最后的希望,所以别惹我.
Lady: Alright.Let's have all my juvenile delinquents this way.
哦,你.我说这边来,公主.
I'm your last hope so don't tick me off.Oh you.I said this way Princess.
韦伯斯特:她可不是你的少年犯.
Webster: She's not one of your juvenile delinquents.
这位阔小姐是到贫民窟来视察的.
She's a person of substance who's just slumming down here.
开萝尔:不错.
Carol: That's right.
女士:好极了.我们需要像你这样的.
Lady: Great.We need people like you.
韦伯斯特:这些白人也让我过敏.
Webster: These white people get on my nerves too.
开萝尔:你在取笑我.
Carol: You're making fun of me.
韦伯斯特:不.只是个玩笑.你是西维尔医生的女儿,是吗?
Webster: No.That was a joke.You're Doctor Seavers daughter, aren't you?
开萝尔:是的.你怎么知道的?
Carol: Yeah.How did you know?
韦伯斯特:今天上午我把你的耳环给你.
Webster: I returned your ear ring this morning.
开萝尔:哦.哦,是的.对.当然是.尼珂,是不是?
Carol: Oh.Oh yes.Right.Of course.Nick isn't it?
韦伯斯特:不,不是.我叫韦伯斯特.
Webster: No it isn't.It's Webster.
开萝尔:韦伯斯特,尼珂,他们非常接近.
Carol: Webster, Nick, they are very close.
韦伯斯特:你不注意别人,是吗?
Webster: You don't notice people do you?
开萝尔:哦,这不是针对个人的.我连重要的人物都不注意.
Carol: Oh, it's nothing personal.I don_t notice important people either.
韦伯斯特:啊哈.
Webster: Uh hu.
开萝尔:不.对不起.
Carol: No.I'm sorry.I'm just a little uncomfortable.
我只是有点不舒服.我是说这有只全是枪的桶.
I mean there is a bucket of guns right here.
韦伯斯特:那么为什么你自愿来这?
Webster: Well why are you volunteering right here?
开萝尔:哦,我不是自愿的.
Carol: Oh, I'm not volunteering.
我父亲把我拖到这儿来,这样我可能有点同情心.
My father dragged me down here so I could get some sensitivity.
韦伯斯特:现在还早?你真幸运,
Webster: Still early in the day hu?
今天我是自愿来这里的.
Lucky for you you are here on a day I volunteer.
开萝尔:哦,你是一个自愿者?哦,放松了.我还以为我再次说漏了嘴.我一时把你看作他们中的一个.
Carol: Oh, you're a volunteer?Oh what a relief.I thought I'd put my foot
in my mouth again.For a second there I thought you were one of them
韦伯斯特:谁?哦,上帝禁止的.
Webster: Who?Oh heaven forbid no.
开萝尔:我懂得你说的.我是说,这些人怎么了?
Carol: I know what you are saying.I mean what is it with these people?
韦伯斯特:我知道.他们找不到工作?
Webster: I know.Can't they get a job?Can't they be respectable?
他们不会受人尊敬?我认为他们是想用这些会诊来愚弄自己.
I guess they just like to fool themselves with all these sessions.
开萝尔:我明白了.
Carol: I know.
杰森:韦伯斯特,我们不得不推迟你两点的会诊.
Jason: Webster, we've got to put back your two o' clock session.
他们把米勒医生困住了.
They've got Doctor Miller cornered.
开萝尔:两点的会诊.你是他们中的一个?
Carol: Two o clock session.You are one of them?
韦伯斯特:哦哦哦!
Webster: OOOh!
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
韦伯斯特:我的假释官说,如果我拿到相当于高中的证书,
Webster: My parole officer says I can get six months off my probation
我还可以减去半年缓刑.
if I get a High School Equivalency Certificate.
杰森:那么你准备怎么做?
Jason: So what are you going to do?
韦伯斯特:学习.
Webster: Study.
杰森:是呀.我希望我的大儿子也在假释.行,
Jason: Yeah.I wish my oldest son was on parole.Alright Webster.
韦伯斯特.今天我们就谈到这儿.
That's all the time we have for today.And uh, I'm real proud of you.
而且啊,我真为你骄傲.去年你有没有想过要再上学?
Last year did you think you'd be going back to school?
韦伯斯特:没有.
Webster: No way.
杰森:嗨,开萝尔.你干的怎么样?
Jason: Hey Carol, how are you doing?
开萝尔:我把武器都还了,但是还有一个.
Carol: I gave back all the weapons, but there was one extra.
女士:是我的.
Lady: That's mine.
杰森:以为我们有突破了.
Jason: Thought we had a break through.
开萝尔:我在复印机里找到这个.我想这是篇英语作文.
Carol: I found this in the copy machine.I think it's an English paper.
韦伯斯特:你没有读吗?
Webster: You didn't read it did you?
开萝尔:没有.
Carol: No.
韦伯斯特:那么这些红色标记是什么呀?
Webster: Then what are all these red marks?
开萝尔:好了.我读了,也改了.习惯这么做.
Carol: Ok.I read it and corrected it.Force of habit.
韦伯斯特:那么你觉得怎么样?
Webster: Well what did you think?
开萝尔:很感人,也引人注目.
Carol: It was moving and compelling.
韦伯斯特:特别对于街头孩子,是吗?
Webster: Especially for a street kid, right?
开萝尔:听着,我还没说,
Carol: Look, I'm not saying that the spelling wasn't atrocious and grammar
拼写错误,
awful.And I've never heard the word 'mother' used quite so colorfully.
语法也糟糕.而且我还从没看到过"娘"这个词被运用的如此多姿多彩.
But the ideas behind it,
但是主题,
when you are deciding whether or not to rob a liqueur store,
当你决定是否抢劫酒铺时,我知道你当时的感受.
I knew how you were feeling.
我花了两个半月的时间才决定选择我的专业.
It took me two and a half mo0nths to pick my major.
我是说,这样的决定会影响你的一生.
I mean decisions like that can affect your whole life.
韦伯斯特:天哪!
Webster: Golly!
开萝尔:你又在取消我了?
Carol: You're making fun of me again?
韦伯斯特:没有.只是因为你是第一个读它的人.
Webster: No.It's just that you are the first person who's read it.
开萝尔:韦伯斯特:写的好.
Carol: Webster, it's good.
韦伯斯特:你能帮我改好点吗?
Webster: Can you help me make it better?
开萝尔:我现在走了.
Carol: I'm leaving now.
Jason: Carol銆侣ey, it's Saturday night.What are you doing going out?
杰森:开萝尔?嗨,今天是周六晚上.你出去干什么?
开萝尔:别担心.不是约会.
Carol: Don't worry.It's not a date.
杰森:行了,你19岁了.你没有必要告诉我,你去哪,和谁去,去干啥,什么时候回来.
Jason: Come on, you're nineteen.You don't have to tell me where you are going.Who you are going with.What you are going to be doing.When you are coming back.
开萝尔:很好.
Carol: Good.
杰森:因为我为你自豪,开萝尔.
Jason: Cos I'm proud of you Carol.I was real proud of you today.
今天我真的为你自豪.你去了免费诊所,
The way you came down to the free clinic and you saw the way those people
而且你认为那些人和我们没什么两样.他们只需要一点信任和信心.
are just like the rest of us.They just need a little trust and faith.
开萝尔:谢谢你.不是我不需要告诉你,
Carol: Thank you.And not that I need to tell you but I'm meeting with
但是我是去见韦伯斯特,帮他修改文章.
Webster to help him with his English paper.
杰森:哦,韦伯斯特.你是去他的夜校?
Jason: Oh Webster.Are you going over to his night school?
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
杰森:图书馆?
Jason: Library?
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
杰森:不不.就你们俩?
Jason: No no.Just the two of you?
开萝尔:哦,对不起.
Carol: Oh, I'm sorry.
你以为是在诊所我认识的韦伯斯特,
You think it's the Webster I know from the clinic, but its not.
但是不是的.他是哥伦比亚大学的韦伯斯特.
It's Webster Thornhill from Columbia.
杰森:哦,知道了.哦,好的.哦,很好.玩得开心.
Jason: Oh yeah.Oh good.Ok great.You have a good time.
开萝尔:爸爸,我真不敢相信.
Carol: Dad, I can't believe this.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
开萝尔:是同一个韦伯斯特.
Carol: It's the same Webster.
杰森:我不是伪君子.
Jason: I am not a hypocrite.
开萝尔:毕竟你总是对我说要尊重别人,但是我想和他见面,
Carol: After all this talk about me respecting people and I want to meet
你却担心了.
with him and you are upset.
杰森:这只是因为你并不了解韦伯斯特的一切.我是说,
Jason: It's just that you don't know everything there is to know about
他还在假释,而且……你是对的.我是伪君子.
Webster.I mean, he is on parole and ...You're right.I am a hypocrite.
假如你要尊重什么人,你就应该像尊重其他人一样去尊重他.
And if you are going to respect somebody,
所以我很抱歉.你去吧,帮帮他,
you should respect them as much as y0u would somebody else.So I'm sorry.
玩的开心.好了.
You go and help him and have a good time.Ok
开萝尔:谢谢爸爸.
Carol: Thank you daddy.
杰森:行了.
Jason: Alright.
开萝尔:再见.
Carol: Bye.
杰森:这就是带她去那儿的原因.这是好的.这是件好事.
Jason: That's what I brought her down there for.This is good.
我真为她骄傲.我得告诉麦琪.麦琪,
This is a good thing.I'm proud of her.I can't wait to tell Maggie."
你女儿和一个罪犯出去了.麦琪,
Maggie, your daughter is going out with an ex con"."
哈哈哈,开萝尔和一个罪犯出去了.开萝尔.
Maggie, ha ha ha, Carol is going out with an ex con".Carol!
麦琪:开萝尔哪儿去了?
Maggie: Where's Carol going?
杰森:我不知道.没有任何线索.没有,坦白地说,我没有.没有.
Jason: Don't know.Don't have a clue.No honestly I don't.No.
杰森:快点,麦琪.快点.没时间了.
Jason: Come on Maggie.Come on.Time is running out.
麦琪:这是我能做的最好的了.罪犯.
Maggie: This is the best I can do.E X C O N.
杰森:那是罪犯.好了,直说吧,麦琪.别耍小聪明.我不喜欢你耍小聪明.你已经超过耍小聪明的年纪了.
Jason: That's ex con.Ok, just say it Maggie.Don't try to be cute.I don't like it when you're cute.You are too old to be cute.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: Pardon?
杰森:那个词,麦琪.为什么你用那个词?
Jason: That word Maggie.Why did you use that word?
麦琪:因为这是三倍的分数.
Maggie: Because it is the triple word score.
杰森:哦,是的.它是的.
Jason: Oh, yes.it is.
韦伯斯特:当我获得假释时,我意识到我不再是小偷了.
Webster: When I got paroled, I learned I was no longer a thief.
但是我是谁,我不知道,
And what I am I don't know,
我害怕一切将变得黑暗而无望,
but I fear a dark and desperate time may come when I must define myself
当我必须确定自己是什么的时候.但是唯一进入我脑海的字是小偷.
as something.And the only word that comes to mind is thief.
开萝尔:很好.有一种绝望的感觉.
Carol: So beautiful.There is such a sense of hopelessness.
韦伯斯特:是这样的.
Webster: I'll say.
开萝尔:读剩余的.
Carol: Read the rest.
韦伯斯特:我就写了这么多.
Webster: That is all I got so far.
开萝尔:那么你的结尾怎么写?
Carol: Well what are your ideas for the ending?
韦伯斯特:我不知道.我想也许在高中学习之后,我可以参加一些培训,也许做个为像我这样的孩子的顾问.
Webster: I don't know.I was thinking maybe after this high school thing I could get some training and maybe be a counselor for guys like me.
开萝尔:真的吗?
Carol: Really?
韦伯斯特:是的.城市学院有这样的课程,
Webster: Yeah.City College has this program where you go part time and
在那可以一边学习,一边工作.
you work part time.
而且在一些差的街区有大量的工作,
And there are plenty of jobs in the bad neighborhoods because nobody wants
因为没有人想在那儿工作,而且路程很近.
to work there, and for it would be a short commute.
你打算干什么,开萝尔?
What are you going to do Carol?
开萝尔:我现在还没正确确定我离开哥伦比亚大学之后的生活,顶级法学院,
Carol: I'm not sure exactly beyond Columbia, a top Law School,
然后为大法官工作,
Clerking for the Supreme Court Justice, and not necessarily a woman,
倒不一定是个女法官,但也不排除涉足政坛的可能.
but I wouldn't rule out a career in politics.
韦伯斯特:那么这将是我们最后一起吃饭了?
Webster: So this will be our last meal together.
开萝尔:不会.
Carol: No.
韦伯斯特:再来点咖啡,擦去油污.
Webster: Some more coffee over here to cut the grease.
服务生:我告诉过你别点辣椒.嗨,你以前来过这儿吗?
Waiter: I told you not to order the chilly.Hey, have you been in here before?
韦伯斯特:没有.那就是为什么我点了辣椒.
Webster: No.That's why I ordered the chilly.
服务生:整个晚上我一直在想你的脸.
Waiter: All night long I've been trying to place your face.
韦伯斯特:在这里.
Webster: Well its right here.
服务生:也许我在电视上见过你.
Waiter: Maybe I saw you on Johnny Carson.
开萝尔:听着,我得道歉.我一定看起来像一个…….
Carol: Look, I want to apologize.I must have seemed like such a..
韦伯斯特:公主?
Webster: Princess?
开萝尔:好,好,我是公主.
Carol: Ok, ok, I was a princess.
韦伯斯特:嗨,你别贬低自己.到那种地方去,人们一定对你感到奇怪.
Webster: Hey don't get down on yourself.It must be kind of strange of you to be in this neighborhood.
开萝尔:事实上,我每天去曼哈顿上学.
Carol: Well actually I commute to Manhattan everyday for school.
见过各种令人厌恶的污秽.
I see all kinds of disgusting filth.
韦伯斯特:可在这儿,你不能脸像这样走过他们,
Webster: Well here you don't get to walk over them and keep walking with
而且一直走.
a face like this.
开萝尔:我得告诉你我曾经也生活在这个城市.
Carol: I will have you know that I have lived in the city.
服务生:这个家伙两年前抢过我.
Waiter: That is the guy who mugged me two years ago.
杰森:感谢上帝.好吧,
Jason: Thank god.Alright Maggie, your suspicions were true.
麦琪.你怀疑是对的.我之前什么也不想说,
I didn't want to say anything before because I knew you'd be upset.
因为我怕你着急.但是开萝尔今晚是和一个罪犯出去了.
But Carol tonight has been out with an ex con.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:是的,他是我们免费诊所的病人.
Jason: Yes, somebody I have been working with down at the clinic.
一个强盗.
An armed robber.
麦琪:开萝尔现在和他出去了?
Maggie: Carol is out with him now?
杰森:不,她现在没有和他出去.开萝尔已经平安健全的回家了,就像我知道的她会平安的,而且我认为我们应该为开萝尔重新具有同情心和意识而鼓掌.来来.嗨!
Jason: No, she is not out with him now.She is home safe and sound
like I knew she would be, and we think we should applaud carols new found
sensitivity and awareness.Come on.Hey
迈克:谢谢,谢谢.谢谢.
Mike: Thank you, thank you.Thank you.
麦琪:杰森,你在说?
Maggie: Jason, you were saying?
杰森:开萝尔会没事的.行了,我们了结我们的游戏.
Jason: Carol is going to be fine.Alright, let's just finish the game.
麦琪:开萝尔和一个罪犯出去?
Maggie: Carol is out with an ex con?
杰森:罪犯是个复合词.不算,麦琪.
Jason: Ex con is hyphenated.That doesn't count Maggie.
迈克:电话.
Mike: Telephone.
杰森:对不起.
Jason: Excuse me.
麦琪:不,留个口信,迈克.
Maggie: No, take a message Mike.
迈克:听起来非常重要,妈妈.
Mike: It sounds pretty important mum.
麦琪:这也很重要.
Maggie: So is this.
迈克:伙计们,你们怎么拼写警察局?
Mike: Guys, how do you spell precinct?
警察:你们知道你们的女儿和一个罪犯一起外出吗?
Policeman: Did you know your daughter was going out with a convicted felon?
麦琪:我们中有人知道.
Maggie: Some of us did.
警察:那可不好.
Policeman: That's not good.
杰森:出什么事了?
Jason: What happened?
警察:好吧,发生的事情是这样的,
Policeman: Well what happened was the owner of the diner recognized the
一家餐馆的主人认出嫌疑犯就是两年前抢劫他的人.店主打电话给警察局.
suspect as the person who'd mugged him a couple of years ago.
还用枪对着那家伙.
The owner called the police.Held the guy at gunpoint.
我们赶到之前,嫌疑犯把枪夺走了,
Before we arrived the suspect wrestled the gun away from the guy and then,
他是疯了,他从满是钱的柜子里就拿了10块钱就跑了.
this is crazy he took ten bucks from a full cash register and fled.
麦琪:这是个奇迹,开萝尔没有受伤.
Maggie: It was a miracle Carol wasn't hurt.
警察:是呀.
Policeman: Yeah.
杰森:只是听起来不像是韦伯斯特,韦伯斯特是那种……
Jason: That just doesn't sound like Webster.Webster would be the kind...
麦琪:韦伯斯特!杰森,别!
Maggie: Webster!Jason please!
杰森:开萝尔!
Jason: Carol.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的.你还好吧?
Maggie: Oh honey.Are you ok?
开萝尔:我想是的.
Carol: I think so.
麦琪:哦,我可怜的宝贝.我们回家.
Maggie: Oh my poor baby.Let's go home.
开萝尔:爸爸,我不明白发生了什么事情.
Carol: daddy I don't understand what happened.
麦琪:忘记它吧.
Maggie: Forget about it.
开萝尔:妈妈,我不想忘记这件事.爸爸,怎么发生这样的事情?
Carol: Mum, I don't want to forget about it.Daddy, how could this happen?
杰森:我不知道.
Jason: I don't know.
开萝尔:爸爸,他告诉我,
Carol: Daddy, he was telling me how he wanted to be counselor and help
他如何想做个顾问,去帮助其他孩子.
other kids.We were laughing.
我们正在笑.突然,
And then all of a sudden,
那家伙走了过来,掏出枪对着韦伯斯特,骂他是个贼,"
this guy comes and pulls this gun on him and calls him a thief."
你是个贼,你走到哪儿也是个贼."
You are a thief and that's all you are is a thief".And Webster's eyes changed.
韦伯斯特眼神都变了.像死了一样.
It was like he'd died.
接着他夺过了枪,拿了些钱就跑了.
And then he just grabbed the gun, took some money and left.
麦琪:他是个罪犯,开萝尔.
Maggie: He's a criminal Carol.
开萝尔:妈妈,他不是那样.
Carol: Mum, he is more than that.He was trying.
他正在努力.你可以读一下这篇文章.
I mean you should read this essay.He worked on it so hard.
他写的非常的认真.可他就这么跑了,好象什么都无所谓.
And then he just left it there like it didn't even matter.
爸爸,我不明白.
Daddy, I don't understand.
麦琪:杰森,你来睡觉吗?我还没有对你嚷嚷够呢.
Maggie: Jason, are you coming to bed?I'm not through yelling at you yet.
杰森:不是现在.
Jason: Not right now.
麦琪:好不容易使得开萝尔入睡.
Maggie: I finally got Carol to sleep.
而你知道当她快要入睡的时候对我说了什么吗?
And do you know what she said to me as she was drifting off?
她居然说她很高兴去了你那个倒霉的免费诊所.杰森,
She actually said that she was glad that she went down to that awful clinic.
你在听我说话吗?
Jason are you listening to me?
杰森:她可能已经被杀死.
Jason: She could have been killed.
麦琪:对呀.她可能被杀死.
Maggie: Damn right.She could have been killed.
听着,杰森,我也和你一样,
Look Jason, I want to help the downtrodden people just as much as you do,
希望帮助那些被社会遗忘的人,但是当有机会我们的一个孩子……
but when there is a chance that one of our children...
杰森:麦琪,我把女儿带入危险.这我知道.
Jason: Maggie, I put my daughter in danger.I know that.yes, yes.
是的,是的.那是个愚蠢的想法.
It was a silly idea.My stupid idealism.
我愚蠢的理想主义.我以为只要我去那儿,和那些人一起工作,那样我可以很重要.
I believe that just because I go down there and I work with people,
我就可以改变他们,麦琪.我是个傻瓜.
that I can make a difference.I can change them Maggie.I'm a fool.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我,我从来没叫过你傻瓜.
Maggie: Oh Jason, I, I never called you a fool.
杰森:如果她发生什么事情,麦琪.天哪!
Jason: If anything had happened to her Maggie.God!
麦琪:小甜心,我在我的生活中需要一点你这样愚蠢的理想主义.
Maggie: Sweetheart I need a little of your stupid idealism in my life.
我可能心胸很狭隘.
I can be narrow minded.
但是你知道;合在一起,
But you know what; together we make a pretty balanced person.
我们成为一个完美的平衡人;分下来,我不会对我们两个中的任一个发疯.
Separately, I'm not crazy about either one of us.
杰森:是呀.我总是认为,你知道,
Jason: Yeah.Well I always thought,
我相信,如果你是个好人,
you know I believed that if you were a good person,
如果你尊重别人,如果你真诚,如果你公平和如果你诚实,
if you treat people with respect,
如果你相信上帝,那么没有什么可以伤害到你.没有什么可以伤害到你所爱的人.
if you are sincere and you're fair and you're honest, if you believe in god,
今晚,麦琪,
then nothing can harm you.Nothing can harm the people you love.
我第一次明白,这是啊,我错了.
Tonight Maggie I see for the first time, it's uh, I was wrong.
麦琪:哦,杰森,
Maggie: Oh Jason, just because Webster turned out bad doesn't mean you
就因为韦伯斯特变坏并不意味着你没有拯救过许多人.
haven't helped out a lot of people down there.
杰森:那么麦琪,我怎么知道他们就不能自己变好了呢?
Jason: Well Maggie, how do I know that they wouldn't have gotten better
我怎么就知道我是否重要.
by themselves?How do I know I make a difference?
麦琪:你对我就很重要.
Maggie: You make a difference with me.
杰森:那很甜蜜.我只是,我想我需要单独待会儿.
Jason: That's very sweet.I just, I think I want to be alone for a bit.
麦琪:好吧.杰森,我爱你.杰森:我很高兴.
Maggie: Ok.Jason, I love you.Jason: I'm glad.
韦伯斯特:医生.
Webster: Doc.
杰森:你在这儿干吗?
Jason: What are you doing here?
韦伯斯特:我还能去哪儿?
Webster: Where else can I go?
杰森:那你走错地方了.
Jason: Well you came to the wrong place.
韦伯斯特:我犯了大错.
Webster: I made a big mistake.
杰森:你犯了错!那我呢?
Jason: You made a mistake!What about me?I trusted you Webster.
我信任了你,韦伯斯特.我信任你和我女儿.
I trusted you with my daughter.
韦伯斯特:我没有计划那枪.
Webster: I didn't plan for that gun.
杰森:我不想听这些.我要打电话去警察局.
Jason: I don't want to hear about it.I'm going to call the police.
韦伯斯特:那么开萝尔还好吧?
Webster: Well is Carol alright?
杰森:你在乎什么?
Jason: What do you care?
韦伯斯特:我在乎她!我在乎.
Webster: I care alright damn it!I do.
杰森:你今晚做了些什么,韦伯斯特.
Jason: What were you doing tonight Webster?
韦伯斯特:西维尔医生,今晚,我第一次感到我们谈的那些事,可能会实现.餐厅里的那个家伙又提起了好多年以前的事.他骂我是贼,还说我永远是贼.他深信我是贼.
Webster: Doctor Seaver, tonight for the first time, I saw that all that stuff we talked about could really happen.Then that guy in the diner starts talking about stuff that happened years ago.Saying I was a thief and that was all I was ever going to be.Well he convinced me.
杰森:你更知道自己.
Jason: Well you know better.
韦伯斯特:是啊,医生,但是只有因为是你.那就是我为什么在这.
Webster: Yeah doctor, but only because of you.And that's why I'm here.
杰森:因为我?
Jason: Cos of me.
韦伯斯特:是的,假如你没让我觉得有希望,
Webster: Yeah, I wouldn't feel so awful right now if you hadn't made me
我现在也许会好受些.
feel so good.Would you come down to the police station with me?
你能陪我去警察局吗?我需要你陪我去.
I need you to come with me.
杰森:我去.我去.我陪你去.
Jason: I'll come.I'll come.I'll come with you.
韦伯斯特:我没有想到……任何这些事情发生.我是如此,我很抱歉,医生.(哭)
杰森:我们会帮你度过的.我们会帮你度过的.
00:22:21,200
Webster: I didn't mean for...for any of this to happen.I'm so, I'm sorry doc.(crying) I'm sorry man. Jason: We'll get you through it.We'll get you through it.